

Clare Lim Full Stack Developer

lhy.clare@gmail.com

portfolio-clare.herokuapp.com

linkedin.com/in/clare-lhy

github.com/clarelhy [7]

More than 5 years of experience in a fast-paced environment, trained in hell and always ready to get my hands dirty in the face of challenges. I thrive when given autonomy and freedom to explore and innovate. I work efficiently when trusted to manage and deliver under minimal supervision, both collaboratively and independently. Check out my LinkedIn and web portfolio to know more!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer IDEMIA Singapore Pte Ltd

03/2021 - Present

- Full Stack Developer in SCRUM Turn-key Project Team
- Running SCRUM for border-control turn-key projects
- Web App development with Angular 11 and Node.js
- iOS App development with React Native and Node.js
- CI/CD with GitLab and JIRA, using FastLane for iOS Apps
- Manage and guide interns with development work

Full Stack Software Engineer ST Engineering Electronics Pte Ltd

11/2016 - 03/2021

- Team Lead in SCRUM Turn-key Project Team
- Specialize in GIS 2D Maps for C2 and C3 Systems
- Full stack development with AngularJS and NodeJS
- Delivered and maintained 2D Map API for in-house framework
- Delivered and maintained 8 2D GIS Maps for projects
- Worked directly with PM, BA, UI/UX, clients, BD and pre-sales
- Managed both local and offshore development teams

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Double Major in Computer Science, Cyber Forensics & Information Security and Management

Murdoch University

05/2015 - 09/2016

 Diploma in Infocomm and Network Engineering Temasek Polytechnic

05/2012 - 05/2015

SKILLS

SCRUM Full Stack Development

Angular 1 / 2+ Node.js REST API

JavaScript / TypeScript CI / CD

FastLane NoSQL GitLab / JIRA

React / React Native 2D GIS Map

ACHIEVEMENTS

ST Top Talent Group (2019 - 2021)

Director's List Award (2014)

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Chinese

Full Professional Proficiency

Cantonese

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Tattoo Music Gigs/Concerts

Gaming Space Exploration Arcade